## **MATTHEW VANDEUSEN**

Client Services and Technology Account Management Professional

### **Professional Summary**

Client focused software and technology professional. Constantly expanding expertise and using this knowledge and skillset to strengthen relationships with client base. Collaborating with multiple stakeholders, maximizing our resources to meet and exceed clients' goals and challenges.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Client Services Representative**

Tickets.com, Remote

March 2014 – Present

- Tailor approach to utilize our software and technology for portfolio of clients covering a broad range of size, business needs and expectations including the Major League Baseball teams and many others.
- Conduct daily calls and meetings with clients to discuss needs and strategies for utilizing our software products.
- Collaborate with internal technology teams to convey our clients' enhancement requests and concerns.
- Introduce clients to new software functionality and features through training, documentation and communication tailored to that specific client's business needs and goals.
- Play an active role in using software and technology services to meet all short- and long-term deadlines for clients' ticketing needs.
- Expand knowledge of both Tickets.com evolving technology and ticketing software industry trends in order to allow clients to constantly improve their standing within the field.

### **Software Support Associate**

Tickets.com, Syracuse, NY

January 2013-March 2014

- Team member of a group serving as contact point for over 200 clients. Addressed all clients' inquiries and needs relating to box office setup and online sales configuration.
- Communicated feedback to internal resources about clients' general feedback and enhancement requests.

- <u>matthewvandeusen3@gmail.com</u>
- 607-267-2729
- 26 Free Street Lisbon Falls, Maine, 04252
- in linkedin.com/in/matthewvandeusen

### **EDUCATION**

### Master of Professional Studies Sports Industry Management

Georgetown University Washington, D.C. 2011-2012

# **Bachelor of Arts Political Science**

University of New England Biddeford, Maine 2005 - 2009

### **SKILLS**

Account Management
Software Training
Internal Issue Tracking
Technology Troubleshooting
Creative Problem Solving
Basic Data Management
HTML and CSS
Ticketing Industry Insight

Project Tracking Software

Data Entry

## **MATTHEW VANDEUSEN**

### Client Services and Technology Account Management Professional

- Conducted validations and testing on new software upgrades and features across broad platform of products and services prior to roll out.
- Provided technical support and troubleshooting for both software and hardware items pertaining to all aspects of the client's box office needs.

### **Marketing and Promotions Intern**

Colgate University, Hamilton, NY

October 2012-January 2013

- Developed in-game marketing promotions for Colgate University athletics.
- Implemented strategies to develop interaction between the student body, community and fan base with the athletic programs.

### **Lodging and Hospitality Assistant Manager**

Colgate Inn, Hamilton, NY

July 2012-January 2013

- Oversaw all front desk and lodging operations relating to all aspects of guest and group bookings, check ins, and client needs throughout stay.
- Learned and became proficient in utilizing inn management software to manage all aspects of lodging needs including troubleshooting and employing key features.
- As the point of contact, collaborated with staff across organization to address any client and guest needs related to all aspects of bookings and private events.

### **Gameday Operations Supervisor**

Washington Redskins, Landover, MD September 2011-January 2012

- Oversaw various stadium operations processes on game days throughout the 2011 NFL Season including ticketing access points and guest services.
- Maintained quality checks of various areas of the stadium including staffing and suite services.
- Engaged in weekly stadium operations and guest services meetings to develop strategy for upcoming games.

- matthewvandeusen3@gmail.com
- 607-267-2729
- 26 Free Street
   Lisbon Falls, Maine, 04252
- in linkedin.com/in/matthewvandeusen

### **EDUCATION**

### Master of Professional Studies Sports Industry Management

Georgetown University Washington, D.C. 2011-2012

# **Bachelor of Arts Political Science**

University of New England Biddeford, Maine 2005 - 2009

### **SKILLS**

Account Management
Software Training
Internal Issue Tracking
Technology Troubleshooting
Creative Problem Solving
Basic Data Management
HTML and CSS
Ticketing Industry Insight
Data Entry

Project Tracking Software